Guide to the Central Asia Fellowship Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
Central Asia Fellowship Records
1983-2016
RG 213
Yale University Divinity School Library
16
(40 boxes)
These are the official archives of the Central Asia Fellowship, which was established in 1989 by Christian mission organizations, churches, and individuals coming together to form a network and a resource organization in order to reach Tibetan Buddhist peoples in Bhutan, China, the Commonwealth of Independent States (Russian republics), India, Mongolia, and Nepal. Portions of the archives are restricted due to security concerns.
Central Asia Fellowship
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Central Asia Fellowship, 2009, 2014, 2017
Custodial History
These archives were formerly housed at the University of Edinburgh.
Conditions Governing Access
The portions of this collection that are listed in this finding aid are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
The Central Asia Fellowship was established in 1989 by Christian mission organizations, churches, and individuals coming together to form a network and a resource organization in order to reach Tibetan Buddhist peoples in Bhutan, China, the Commonwealth of Independent States (Russian republics), India, Mongolia, and Nepal. Headquartered in Kathmandu, Nepal, the CAF is not a mission organization in itself but rather a resource center for information, fellowship, training, research, and practical support of projects. The CAF was involved in work with the United Bible Society in the area of Bible translation.
The CAF is run by a Board that is appointed at the Annual General Meeting by vote among the members, and which also appoints a General Secretary and a local Working Committee for the day-to-day work of the organization.
Scope and Contents
Note that the online version of the finding aid for this collection excludes certain sections, due to security concerns. A full copy of the finding is available at the repository. Please contact divinity.library@yale.edu for more information about access to the restricted materials.
This collection contains valuable documentation of the efforts of Christian organizations and individuals to reach Tibetan Buddhist peoples in Asia. The CAF archives form part of the Himalayan collection at Yale Divinity School, which also includes the archives of the United Mission to Nepal, International Nepal Fellowship, and the Nepal Church History Project. The CAF archives were formerly housed at the University of Edinburgh and have been labeled with a classification system. A full listing of the classification system is available in Box 5, Folder 12. Digital versions of many of the documents dating from 1995 to 2002 are available on a CD in Box 19. Digital versions of earlier documents are available on floppy disks in the same box, but may not be useable.
Series I, Pre-CAF Materials, provides useful documentation of early work to reach Tibetan peoples. Many of the individuals involved in this early work were from Scandinavian countries and the Scandinavian influence remained strong in CAF. Series II, Adminstration, contains the core of minutes, reports, and other documentation of the operations of CAF. Much of the correspondence in Series III is with two General Secretaries: Asbjorn Voreland and Grethe Raddum. Series IV, Countries, contains resource material regarding the religion, culture, and language of areas of interest to CAF, as well as documentation of the efforts of Christian organizations in these areas. The remaining series document the CAF's operations and membership information, literature distribution efforts, courses and consultations it arranged, and projects it supported. The Publications of Series X included audio-visual materials as well as printed literature, including, for example, versions of the Jesus film in Dzongkha, Eastern Tamang, Sherpa, Tibetan (Amdo), and Tibetan (Lhasa).
Series XI, Addendum -2015, includes additional publications and documenation of the work of CAF.
Arrangement
I. Pre-CAF Materials (B), 1893-1990
II. Administration (C), 1986-2002
III. Correspondence (D), 1989-1999, n.d.
IV. Countries (E), 1987-1998, n.d.
V. Finances (F), 1986-1999, n.d.
VI. Library (L), 1996-1997, n.d.
VII. Members (M), 1985-2002
VIII. Projects (P), 1988-1998
IX. Training and Teaching (S), 1988-1998
X. Publications (A), 1969-2003, n.d.
XI: Addendum - 2015
XII. Addendum - 2017
Bible -- Translating; Missions -- China -- Tibet Autonomous Region; Missions -- Nepal; Central Asia Fellowship
- Pre-CAF Materials (B), 1893-1990; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  This online finding aid provides a partial listing of materials available in the archives. For more information, please contact the repository.
  - Periodicals and newspapers (B01)
    - Articles, 1950-1973, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
    - Miscellaneous clippings and papers re. Tibet, 1949, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Early pioneers (B02, B03)
    - Theo. Sorensen: Biographical material re. Theo. and Cissi Sorensen, including photocopy of letter from J. Hudson Taylor (1893); Annual Report of the Tibetan Religious Literature Depot (1921-1922); Norwegian language material, 1893-1922, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Faith Prayer and Tract League (Michigan) tracts, and re. E. B. Steiner (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Steiner, E. B.: Including "An Evangelistic Tour to the Tibetan Border" (first printing 1929); "Twenty Days Inside Tibet" (first printing1930); "My Call to Tibet" (1946), 1937-1946, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Sheldon, Martha: "Bhot for Christ" - pamphlet re. Martha Sheldon by Elbert M. Moffat, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Moules, Len: including "Tibeten Border Bulletin" (1946), newspaper clipping, typescript letter, 1944-1946 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Avery, Harold: "The Challenge of Central Asia" - support card, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Ekvall, R.: Typescript essay "Tibetan Religion as Percevied by the Missionary", n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Ladakh: Gergan, Yoseb and Phuntsog, Eliyah: including re. translation of Bible into Tibetan, writings re. their conversion to Christianity by Gergan and Phuntsog, 1935, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Central Asia Mission (B04)
    - Annual reports, publications, correspondence, matps, personnel, including by D. Berger, 1942-1946, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - China Inland Mission (B05)
    - Publications, hand-drawn map, typescript report of visit of Rev. and Mrs. Frank Learner, ca. 1950, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Adminstration (C), 1986-2002; Series II
  The listings for this series are restricted. Contact the repository for more information.
- Correspondence (D), 1989-1999; Series III
- Countries (E), 1987-1998; Series IV
  Some of the listings for this series are restricted. Contact the repository for more information.
  - Russian Republics: General (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Russian Republics: Buryatia, Kalmykia (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Mongolia: General (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Mongolia: Articles (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - China: General (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Nepal: General (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Nepal: Unreached people (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - India (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Other countries (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Maps (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Tibetan Buddhist World (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Finances (F), 1986-1999; Series V
- Library (L), 1996-1997; Series VI
  - Articles (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Book lists (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Periodicals (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Videos (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Members (M), 1985-2002; Series VII
- Projects (P), 1988-1998; Series VIII
- Training and Teaching (S), 1988-1998; Series IX
- Publications (A), 1969-2003, n.d.; Series X
  - Audio-visual Aids (A01)
    - Posters, prints, flipcharts (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Oversize posters (Box 19)
    - Audio cassettes, CDs in Nepali, Tibetan, Bhutanese, Chinese, Mongolian, Indian, Russian (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Audio cassettes, CDs, audiotapes, including Tibetan praise songs (Box 17)
    - Megavoice Microchip Audio Player (Box 17)
    - Video cassettes (VHS/PAL): Jesus Film in Dzongkha, Eastern Tamang, Sherpa, Tibetan (Amdo), Tibetan (Lhasa) (Box 18)
    - Video cassettes (VHS/PAL): "Tibetan Travels"; "Good News for You"; "You Too Can Reach Tibet"; "The Art of Dying"; "Quiangic Speaking Tibetan" (Box 18)
    - Video compact discs: Jesus Film in Tibetan (Lhasa and Amdo), "Quiangic Speaking Tibetan" (Box 18)
    - Slide set: "Tibetan Travels" (Box 18)
    - Calendars (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Oversize calendar (Box 19)
    - Postcards, cards, bookmarks (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Tracts (A02)
    - In English (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Nepal: Nepali, Lhomi, Lowa (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Tibet: Lhasa (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Tibet: Amdo (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Bhutan: Dzongkha, Tshangla (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - China: Mandarin (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Mongolia: Mongolian (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - India: Hindi (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Russia: Russian (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bibles, New Testaments, Gospels (A03)
    - Tibet: Tibetan- Kham, Amdo (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Tibet: English/Tibetan bilingual; English/Tibetan/Chinese trilingual (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Tibet: Moravian/Ladakhi (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Tibet: Tibetan-Lhasa New Testament (Box 19)
    - Bhutan: Dzongkha (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Bhutan: Tshangla (Box 19)
  - Hymn books (A04)
    - Tibet: Tibetan -Lhasa, Kham, Amdo (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Books and articles (A05)
    - English: Books, people group profiles, discipleship Bible course (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - English: Book: Poles Apart Contextualizing the Gospel in Asia, 1998 (Box 19)
    - English: prayer materials (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - English: seminars, articles, theses (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Nepal: Nepali, Lhomi, Lowa, Sherpa (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Tibet: Tibetan - Lhasa, Amdo (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Tibet: ""The Message of Yahweh, Heavenly Father" in Tibetan by Don E. Stanton, 2003 (Box 19)
    - Bhutan: Dzongkha, Tshangla (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - China: Mandarin (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Mongolia: Mongolian (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Swedish (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Language materials (A06)
    - Tibet: Tibetan - Lhasa (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ordering information (A07)
    - Tibetan literature and cassette list (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Health
    - Tibetan - Lhasa (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Addendum - 2015, Series XI
  - Regarding work of CAF
    - Brochures: Milestone 25; Global Prayer Day for Tibet and Tibetans; Global Day of Prayer for Tibet, 2009-2010, no date (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - CAF Prayer Bulletin (2 issues), 2007, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - "Call of CAF" newsletter (14 issues), 2009-2013 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Prayer calendars, 2007-2012 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Cards and bookmarks, 2008, no date (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Publications and program material
    - Books
      - B1204, B1205: B1501: (Box 20, Folder 6)
        B1204: A Concise History of Tibetan People; B1205: Aspect of Tibetan History Lungta; B1501: Among Tibetan Women: Tibetan Practices related to Birth and Name Giving
      - B1502, B1504, B1505 (Box 20, Folder 7)
        B1502: The Implications of Cultural Childbirth Practices on the Health of Women and their Newborns in Bhutan; B1504: Evangelism and Christian Education in Nepal in Light of Orality and Increasing Literacy; B1505: Comparing Christianity and Tibetan Buddhism 2008
      - B2101E, B2101FR, B2202 (Box 20, Folder 8)
        B2101E: The Tibetan Buddhist World (Eng); B2101FR: The Tibetan Buddhist World (French); B2202: Bravery
      - B2203, B2206, B2305 (Box 20, Folder 9)
        B2203: The Path to Enlightenment; B2206: Tibetan Buddhism and Christianity; B2305: Tibetan Buddhism: Ways of Understanding a Complex; Religion, Paths to Present the Gospel
      - B3201, B3202CN, B3202 (Box 21, Folder 1)
        B3201: Cross Cultural Training Manual Part One (English); B3202CN: Cross Cultural Training Manual Part 1 (Chinese); B3202: Cross Cultural Training Manual Part 2 (English)
      - B3202CN, B3204, B3277 (Box 21, Folder 2)
        B3202CN: Cross Cultural Training Manual Part 2 (Chinese); B3204: Poles Apart: Contextualizing the Gospel in Asia; B3277: Sharing Christ in the Tibetan Buddhist World, 2006 Revised, Asian Edition, English (3rd international edition)
      - B3277CN (Box 21, Folder 3)
        B3277CN: Sharing Christ in the Tibetan Buddhist World, Chinese Translation
      - B3277KO (Box 21, Folder 4)
        B3277KO: Sharing Christ in the Tibetan Buddhist World: Korean
      - B277RU, B3301, B3302 (Box 21, Folder 5)
        B277RU: Sharing Christ in the Tibetan Buddhist World, Russian Translation; B3301: The Name Above All; B3302: One Refuge (for the people of the world's highest plateau)
      - B3303, B3303E, B3304, B3304e (Box 22, Folder 1)
        B3303: A Tibetan Monk's Story (Central Tibetan); B3303E: A Tibetan Monk's Story (English); B3304: God Spoke Tibetan (Tibetan Literary); B3304e: God Spoke Tibetan (English)
      - B3305, B3307, B3311sh (Box 22, Folder 2)
        B3305: From Darkness to Light; B3307: Detour from Tibet; B3311sh: Blessings of God: Sherpa (Solu) - Konchof-gi-Molam
      - B6102, B6201 (Box 22, Folder 3)
        B6102: Catechism in Buryatian; B6201: Streams in the Desert
      - B6302, B6304, B6304E, B6305 (Box 22, Folder 4)
        B6302: His Great Love: Tibetan C/LT; B6304: Good News: This is the path to life and peace (Central Tibetan); B6304E: Good News: This is the path to life and peace (English version); B6305: Questions and Answers - CT
      - B6307, B6308 (Box 22, Folder 5)
        B6307: Ministry to Tibetan Buddhists (booklet); B6308: Freedom from Karma (English)
      - B6309 (Box 22, Folder 6)
        B6309: Firm Foundations Vol. 1
      - B6310, B6315 (Box 23, Folder 1)
        B6310: Firm Foundations Vol. 2; B6315: What is the World Coming To?
      - Unclassified: Tibetan Voices; TB Global Emergency (Chinese); The Future of the World (Tibetan) (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Unclassified: Questions & Answers (Central/Nepal version); Christianity in Bhutan (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Unclassified: Including issue of The Tibet Journal, the Moravian Textbook with Almanack (Nepali), 1991, 2000; 2000; no date (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Music
      - M0002, M0003b (Box 24, Folder 9)
        M0002: Offer A Praise Song (A Collection of 100 Tibetan Hymns psalm and spiritual songs) (Lhasa Dialiect Roman Script Version/English); M0003b: Offer a Praise Songbook - Tibetan Script (green)
      - M0005, M0006, M0202 (Box 31, Folder 6)
        M0005: Tibetan Songbook Music Version with Chinese Characters; M0006: Offer Up a Praise Songbook, Index; M0202: Amdo Tibetan Praise Songs with CD
      - M0011: Offer Up A Praise (CT 2011) (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - M0011AT: Offer A Praise Song - Amdo Tibetan (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - M0105: Praise the name of Jesus w/ CD: New Tibetan Praise Songs; M1001: A New Song Rising in Tibetan Hearts (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - M1014: Kham Worship Songbook (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - M2000: Gospel Communication in Tibetan Song; M2202: Nomadic Amdo Tibetan Glu Folk Songs (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - M8202: Amdo Tibetan Folk Songs with CD (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Children's material
      - C1001 - C1006 (Box 23, Folder 4)
        C1001: Children's Story - Child Who Brings Peace; C1002: Children's Story - Creation of Man and Earth; C1003: Children's Story - Death and Empty Grave; C1004: Children's Story - The Healing of a Crippled Man; C1005: Children's Story - Prodigal Son: The son who returned home; C1006: Children's Story - Tell Everyone About Me
      - C2001: A Selection of Great Bible Stories (Children's Bible) (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - C3001: Yours, children's book; C3002: Pinoccio/Max Lucado: You are special (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Health and social development
      - H1011-H1013 Yeshi the Yak, vol. 1 - vol. 3 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - H1015, H1018, H1020 (Box 23, Folder 8)
        H1015: How to Take a Medical History in Tibetan - Chinese (English/Tibetan/Chinese); H1018: A New Atlas of Leprosy; H1020: Pregnancy Card fold out
      - H2001: Aspects of the Awareness of HIV/AIDS In Qinghai Province China (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Unclassified: Posters (4), Health Laminated, A4 Size (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Unclassified: Pendaba Training (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Language learning
      - L1002: How to Make Tibetan Sounds; L1004: How to Read Tibetan - Central Tibetan Version (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - L1005: How to Read Tibetan - The Genesis Reader (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - L1006: A Beginning Textbook of Lhasa Tibetan; L1006: A Beginning Textbook of CT Audio (Christmas Songs) (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - L1104: How to Read Tibetan - All China Edition (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - L1301: Tibetan-English Colloquial Primer: Kham Dialect; L2001KO: Introduction to Tibetan Grammar In Korean (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - L3001a: Key Spiritual Terms, PC/Mac CD (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - L0560: A Preliminary Sociolinguistic Study of Tibetan Dialects (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Unclassified: songbooks, no date
    - Prayer materials
      - P0001: Developing a Prayer Strategy - A Dawn Resources for the Twenty-First Century (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - P0003, P0003A, P1001 (Box 25, Folder 4)
        P0003: Mobilize Your Church for Tibetan Peoples: A practical guide…with the resources to do it.; P0003A: Mobilize Your Church for Tibetan Peoples (PC/Mac data CD) (Mobilization Guide); P1001: Strongholds of Central Tibetans: A 31-Day Prayer Guide
      - P1155, P1201, P1201CN (Box 25, Folder 5)
        P1155: Amdo Prayer Calendar (Where does my help come from? -> Pray 30 days for the Amdo Tibetans); P1201: 30 Days of Prayer for the Amdo Tibetans: Updated Version, 2005 (English); P1201CN: 30 Days of Prayer for the Amdo Tibetans: Updated Version, 2005 (Chinese)
      - P1301, P2002: (Box 25, Folder 6)
        P1301: Pray for the People of Nepal: A 30 Day Prayer Guide for the Unreached Peoples of Nepal; P2002: A Billion Wait…: A Prayer Guide for the Buddhist World
    - Scripture
      - S2401Ts: The New Testament in Tshangla (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - S2402Dz: New Testament in Dzongkha (Red) (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - S2404DZ: New Testament in Dzongkhar (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - S2501: NT in Inner Mongolian (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - S3001: Tri-lingual Gospel of John: Who is this man? (3 languages); S3005: Exploring the way to Eternal life with Tibetan (CT); S3005C: Exploring the Way to Eternal Life with Tibetans (CT-Chinese) (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - S3005E, S3006, S3008 (Box 27, Folder 2)
        S3005E: Exploring the way to eternal life with Tibetans (English); S3006: The Gospel of John (Tibetan language); S3008: Gospel of Mark (CT-LL): New version with Chinese text in the front page
      - S3009, S3011, S3012 (Box 27, Folder 3)
        S3009: Jesus Talks to Tibetans; S3011: Luke and Acts(Old classical)- Shanghai; S3012: Songs from Mount Zion (Lhasa Tibetan)
      - S3013: Luke & Acts (CT-LL) (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - S3200: Ten Epistles from the New Testament: Trial Edition (Written Tibetan Mid-level) (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - S3201: Luke and Acts: Trial Edition (Tibetan Literary) (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - S3202: Luke and Acts: Trial Edition (Tibetan Literary) (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - S3203: Mark and John: Trial Edition (WT-ML) (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - S3204: Gen/Luke ML with Chinese (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - S3302sh: Gospel Luke in Sherpa; S3401: Bible Stories (Tsangla/ Bhutan): Sharchhokpa Christian Fellowship (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - S3402DZ: Four Gospels (Dzongkhar) - Red (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - S3701LD, S3702LD, S3703LD (Box 28, Folder 5)
        S3701LD: Gospel of Mark in Ladhakhi (Gospel according to Mark in Colloquial Ladakhi); S3702LD: 1 & 2 Timothy,Titus and Philemon (in Colloquial Ladhaki); S3703LD: Letters to the Hebrews in Ladhaki
      - S3704LD: Paul's letters to the Galatians and The letter of James (in Colloquial Ladhaki); S4001CN: He Lived Among Us - CT (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - S4001: He Lived Among Us; S5001: Bible Guide (CT/LL/Chinese) (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - S5006E, S5007, S5007E (Box 29, Folder 1)
        S5006e: Exploring the Good News of Grace with Tibetans: Studies in Galatians (English); S5007: Exploring the Bible with Tibetans; S5007e: Exploring the Bible with Tibetans
      - S5008, S5008LH, S5008SH, S5009 (Box 29, Folder 2)
        S5008E: Power to Save: Jesus Christ Has Power to Save Us (CT-LL/English); S5008LH: Power to Save in Lhomi; S5008SH: Power to Save in Sherpa; S5009: An Introduction to the Bible
      - S5009E, 3 Unclassified Books (Box 29, Folder 3)
        S5009E: An Introduction to the Bible (English); Unclassified: Good News: This Is the Path to Life and Peace; Unclassified: The Gospel of John; Unclassified: Gospel of Mark, small green, CT
      - Unclassified: 11 volumes - Bible and Bible portions
    - Tracts
      - T0212, T0213, T0217, T0223, T0224, T0224Dz, T0228 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        T0212: Are you Happy - Dzonkha; T0213: The Bridge - Tibetan; T0217: The Cross - CT; T0223: Good News, Creation to Christ; T0224: Heart of Man (CT); T0224Dz: Heart of Man (Dzongkha); T0228: His Story, Book 2 (Tibetan)
      - T0228EN, T0230, T0239, T0244, T0249, T0251, T0252, T0254, T0503 (Box 29, Folder 5)
        T0228EN: His Story, Book 2; T0230: It is a Great Life! - CT; T0239: Noah, The Time is Near - CT; T0244: Prodigal Son tract - CT; T0249: Story of Jesus - Life of Jesus (Tibetan language); T0251: The Way of Salvation - (wide) Tibetan Colloquial; T0252: The Way of the Cross CT; T0254: Way to Heaven, The, CT; T0503: The Saviour for All Nations (Rotoiti Realities Educational Series Book 3)
      - T3001, T3002, T3003, T3004Mn, T3005, T3006, T4003Dz, T6101, T6201, T6301 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        T3001: What is sin? (Kelsang tract); T3002: Woman (White with black print, very small); T3003: Step up to Life - in Tibetan; T3004Mn: After Death - Nyeshang-ge; T3005: Who is Jesus? (Kelsang tract); T3006: In the beginning God created heaven and earth (Kelsang tract); T4003Dz: WWYG (Picture of Couple walking) Dzongkha: Which way you are going; T6101: The Lord's Prayer / Not counted but given out for free; T6201: The Apostle's Creed; T6301: The Experience of the Ultimate Truth (Michael Graham), Tibetan
      - T6304, T6304e, T6305, T6306 (Box 29, Folder 7)
        T6304: Encounter with the Guru/ 7 true Stories (Tibetan); T6304e: Encounter with the Guru / 7 true stories (English); T6305: Creation Story / for free; T6306: Easter Greeting
      - Unclassified Tracts (7) (Box 29, Folder 8)
        Buddha, Marx, or Christ (Tibetan); God's Way of Salvation, Amdo Tibetan; Heart of Man (Nepali); Jesus The Same Yesterday Today and Forever: Good news told by Luke; Life Of Christ (Zongkhar); The Way to God - Dzongkha; Step up to life- in TB.
    - Research
      - R1002, R1003, R1004, R1007 (Box 25, Folder 7)
        R1002: The Khambas: Kham Tibetans (A People Group Profile); R1003: Amdo Tibetans (People Group Profile); R1004: Qiangic Speaking Tibetans - PG Profile; R1007: Tibetan of Exiles Karnataka: Karnataka Missions Network (People Profile Series)
      - Unclassified: Siberian Shamanistic Traditions Among the Kham-Magars of Nepal; Tibetan Buddhist Peoples in the CIS, 1975; 2000
    - Audio-visual material
      - A1001:Full of Grace, Tibetan Gospel Songs; A1004:Serenity Songs (Cassette) (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - A2001: Full of Grace (CD) (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - A1852: Good News for You / Red version (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - A2002: Offer Up a Praise Song, set of 10 CDs (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - A2004: Serenity Songs (CD); A2005: Repentance (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - A2006, A2011, A2012 (Box 30, Folder 4)
        A2006: Eternity; A2011: Grace of Father; A2012: There's Non Like You
      - A2013, A2106, A2202 (Box 30, Folder 5)
        A2013: Dhendup NT Gospel Song; A2106: Kham Christmas Songs (CD); A2202: Praise (Amdo Worship songs II); A2203: Compassion (Amdo Worship songs I)
      - A2301sh, A2401, A4401Ts (Box 30, Folder 6)